And a very serious person, too, I have to tell you.
I've been watching him for a long time.
Is Andy here?
That's what I thought.
Hello, Andy.
I thought that was you.
You're looking better than you do out on those streets, huh?
You look much better.
It's nice to have you.
You feel a little safer here, I think, maybe.
Well, not that safe, because you have them.
You have to worry about them.
But thank you very much.
Andy Noah has been repeatedly beaten by Antifa,
and including one assault that left him with a brain hemorrhage.
Only days ago, Nick Sauter was assaulted in Portland
by a flag-burning mob.
And we've made it a one-year penalty for inciting riots.
We took the freedom of speech away,
because that's been through the courts.
And the courts said, you have freedom of speech.
But what has happened is when they burn a flag,
it agitates and irritates crowds.
They've never seen anything like it on both sides.
And you end up with riots.
So we're going on that basis.
We're looking at it not from the freedom of speech, which
I always felt strongly about, but never passed the courts.
This is what they do, is they incite.
When you burn an American flag, you incite tremendous violence.
We have many examples of it, many, many examples of it.
And it's actually down on tape.
And you see things happen that just don't happen,
unless it's a flag that's burning.